Are you ready for this?
Yeah.
Ready as I'll ever be.
Okay, Asuna.
A couple reminders before I log you in.
You're using Super User Account 01,
Stacia, the Goddess of Creation.
You'll have admin privileges that include
unlimited manipulation of the landscape.
But be careful with it.
When you change the terrain,
the flow of the mnemonic
data between your STL and the
Underworld's main visualizer
is going to be massive.
I'm talking overloading
your Fluctlight massive.
You should be fine if you change
the terrain up a few times.
Just try not to overdo it.
You'll know you are if
your head starts hurting.
If it does, stop. Got it? Got it.
All right.
It's up to you now.
Go get him.
See you in a bit.
I want your way I
want your
way I want your way I want your
It's time to go to the end of the day,
it's time to go to the end of the day.
I can't wait for this answer,
but it's not a matter of time.
It's not a matter of time,
but I can't wait for it.
I can't wait for it.
I guess I overdid it on the first try.
Whatever, now that I'm
here, I have to find Kirito.
Lady Stacia?
Are you her?
The goddess, Stacia?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm definitely not a goddess.
But you, I mean, you
just performed a miracle.
Everyone owes you their lives.
You saved the guards and the priest
and me and my mentor, Kirito, too.
Actually, Kirito is the reason I'm here.
I need to see him now.
So please, take me to him.
I know he's not well,
but I think I can help.
So let me see him.
Right.
Come with us.
Kirito?
It's alright, Kirito.
I'm here now.
Thank you both, for keeping him
safe and letting me see him.
Um, if you're not Lady
Stacia, then who are you?
And where are you from?
My name is Asuna.
I'm human, just like you.
And I come from the same place as Kirito.
Not from this world.
Another one.
You're not from here?
And neither is he?
But what world?
The only other one is Heaven.
Is that where you're from?
The home of the three
goddesses of creation?
The gods who control the
elements and the angels?
Whoa, hold on.
He and I aren't from heaven
or any place like it.
I'm sorry.
It's kind of complicated to explain.
Maybe the best thing would be for me
to talk to whoever's in charge here.
Can you take me to them?
Yes, of course.
Please follow us.
We'll take you right to them.
Don't worry, okay?
I'll be right back. Promise.
I'll figure this out somehow.
Wait!
She means no harm, m 'lady!
She's not the enemy!
She's here to help, Lady Alice!
Alice?
Who are you?
What do you want with Kirito?
Back off, now!
Kirito is mine, understand? Ridiculous!
Be gone from here!
Well, well, well.
Now that is a heck of a sight.
Two beautiful flowers in bloom.
So gorgeous.
So dangerous.
why do you stop me uncle do not trust her
she is a spy for the enemy would you relax
kiddo she's definitely not working for the
bad guys didn't you see
what happened out there
she saved everyone's lives
including mine
here they come
this rainbow appeared when it hit the
ground it cracked it open for a hundred
miles it made a gap so wide those pugilists
couldn't even jump it we were this close
to being wiped out and she stopped it
there's no denying that we owe this lady
our thanks what are you implying she is
either an enemy spy or some filthy heretic
posing as a divine entity but there is
no way she is the goddess stacia didn't
say she was think about it if this little
lady was a real goddess she'd be scarier
than the pontifex she'd break you in half
for being rude to her then she'd chuck
your ass into that pit she conjured
true
i may look it
but i'm not a goddess
i'm a human being just like
you that said i am from
another world and i know
things about your situation
you don't we should hear
her out in fact the other
knights in the unit captains
should be part of this we
can discuss it over some
tea right as you wish great
now that that's settled i
need your help ladies get
some tea and some booze for
me and bring it back to my
tent you might as well stay
for the meeting too yes sir
Let me be clear
If you would like to see Kirito,
you must ask my permission first
His safety is my responsibility,
regardless of who you are
That does it I don't need
your permission to see
him He's not yours Perhaps
he should decide that
Yes, perhaps he should
Wow, that's all we needed,
more tension Oh wow,
time to go and boil some water You start
that, and I'll get the liquor jug, okay?
Okay.
But Kitty Toe's my mentor.
It's nice to meet you all?
My name is Asuna, and I come
from a world outside yours.
A human world, but you
can't physically get to it.
My home, the real world, and yours,
the underworld, are two totally
separate planes of existence.
As we speak, there's a battle
going on in the real world.
It's between two groups, and they're both
fighting for control of the underworld.
I'm here on behalf of one of the groups.
They're called Wrath.
Is that why you're here, then?
To take over our world and rule over it?
No, not at all.
My group and I, we want
to protect the Underworld.
The people we're fighting against
don't care about this place.
They just want one of your people.
And when they find them, they'll capture
them and bring them into our world.
Then, destroy yours.
That's monstrous.
I don't believe this.
How do we know she speaks the truth?
Because it's possible.
The dark territory
surrounds the human empire
it's basically a whole
nother world from ours.
A place with folks who just want to
invade and destroy us few of us have
ever seen it or been To it but it's
as real as our side of the mountains
and now we find out there's another
World out there I say sure why not
you said these folks you're fighting
are looking for someone specific.
You got any idea who that could be?
I am the one?
So that's what this Priestess
of Light stuff's about.
Look, there isn't much time left.
There's only one way to
keep the Underworld safe,
and that's for Alice to return to
the real world with me as quickly?
as possible.
Once the enemy finds out she's not here,
they'll give up and leave your world alone.
You must be joking!
You want me to run away to
your so-called real world?
To abandon my people when
they need me the most?
I would never!
I am an Integrity Knight!
My one and only duty is to
protect the human empire!
And you'd be doing that.
I'm sorry.
I wish there were another way.
But if the enemy from the real
world finds you, they'll take you.
And then everything here, the people,
the land, the sky, everything,
they will erase it all.
We have to go right now before
they find you. Hold on there.
It seems your information's a
bit out of date, little lady.
The enemy from your world?
Yeah, they already found her.
Everything makes a lot more sense now.
It all fits the Priestess of
Light and the Dark God Vecta.
That's why he suddenly
showed up to lead his army.
But he's not a Dark God.
He came from the real world just like you.
Dark God Vecta.
Then the Dark Territory has superuser
accounts, and they're not locked.
Um, may I ask something?
Regarding this Priestess of Light,
I have never heard of her before.
So why do these invaders from the real
world want Alice of all people so badly?
She broke the seal in her right eye.
You know of what happened?
And the seal? But how?
The central cathedral is indestructible,
made of the hardest material here.
I think how fun it would
be to slice through it.
Then all of a sudden, I feel a
horrible pain in my right eye.
I wonder how many of us here
experienced the same thing as her.
I'm sure at some point you all had doubts
about the Pontifex or
some of the Church's laws.
You saw flashes of red light in your
right eye, and then you felt the pain.
It hurt so bad it made you forget what
you were thinking about, didn't it?
You know what happens if you keep
thinking those blasphemous thoughts?
The pain gets worse and worse until
it's searing your brain, and then...
Your vision turns red, and
your right eye explodes.
Then, did your eye...
To put a stop to Administrator's rule,
I knew I would be confronting
Chudelkin as well as her.
To muster the resolve to do
so, I had to lose my eye.
Come to think of it, I recall
Administrator saying something.
Something about the seal of the eye.
I believe she said, code...
That's it!
Code 871!
She looked right at me, and that is what
she called the seal of the right eye.
I believe she also said it was installed.
I did not know what she meant at the
time, but could this code 871 seal?
Be a product of the real world a seal
871 it must be an inhibitor but why
would Rath install that in them in
the end it would just get in the way
Rath's ultimate goal was to make an AI
with true intelligence the underworld
was created for that purpose and that's
why Ki-Kuoka and Hika let it evolve
for centuries internally if the whole
point of this simulation was to give the
AIs the opportunity to demonstrate free
will forcing them into obedience with
an inhibitor defeats the purpose unless
the seal is a kind of sabotage are the
people in the ocean turtles main con
behind this no saboteur must be someone
with wrath they could be with us in
subcon i have to tell kikwoka but there's
no terminal here i could suicide out but
i need alice to save kirito what do i do
You know what to do.
Is something wrong with you?
No, I'm fine.
Alice is right.
That Code 871 seal was
put there by someone.
Someone from my world.
And they're on the enemy's side.
How do we get rid of the seal?
Is there a way to do it without
blowing out someone's eyeball?
I'm sorry, but I don't know of another way
to disable it from inside the Underworld.
Alright, based on what
we know about this enemy,
they only want someone who's got the
willpower to break the seal of the right eye.
Why one of us?
Do all the folks in your
world have a seal like we do?
No, that's something
we've never had to suffer.
In fact,
I believe the only point of difference
between the Underworld and the
real-worlders is how you're being
forced to obey your laws and orders.
Whoever's responsible for the seal in your
eye doesn't want you having free will.
They're afraid of this priestess
of light, as you call her,
because someone like that could
ruin whatever they had planned.
And if she appeared in my world,
your priestess of light would be
considered extremely valuable.
I still don't get what the fuss is about.
You said so yourself just now.
There ain't a whole lot of
difference between our kinds.
The only thing is a seal of the
right eye, except for Alice here.
She broke her seal, and according to you,
she's no different than
a real-worlder now.
You got a world full of your kind already,
so why are you and your enemies so
obsessed with snatching up little Alice?
And once you do get her in your world,
what are you planning on doing with her?
Sorry.
I can't say.
Not right now.
She should see the real world first.
Then she can decide what
she wants to do for herself.
It's not heaven.
It's no paradise either.
Not even close.
Compared to here, it's not as tranquil.
It's not as pretty or as clean.
But still, there are good
things about my world.
The people, for one.
There's some who'd want to exploit you,
but there's more who'd
want to protect this world.
Just like Kirito.
I have questions, but
they can wait until later.
First, we must focus on
breaking the enemy army.
And then we must make peace
with the Dark Territory.
I will not go anywhere until then.
Fine.
Besides,
now that we know Vecta's
from the real world,
it'd be dangerous for us to
leave the safety of your army.
He'll be expecting that, I'm sure.
That said, I'll join
your people in the fight.
As for Vecta, let me
deal with him. All right!
We're glad to have you along.
About your skill, how you split
the ground open like that.
Is there a limit to using it? There is.
I can alter the landscape like
that one or two more times.
But that's it.
This is our world, remember?
Protecting it is our
responsibility, not hers.
Let us show her what we are capable of.
Yes, yes, you are right.
Lady Asuna is not a god.
She just told us she was human
like the rest of us if she
is willing to fight hard Then
we shall fight even harder.
I support this if only to fight
that pugilist again. You're right.
It's our world It's
our duty to protect it.
And I'll protect this
world, Kitty doll up,
from the hijackers aboard the ocean
turtle and from wrath if I have to!
I knew you would come.
All right.
I will let you see him, and I will
tell you everything I know of him.
In return, however, if you are agreeable,
you must tell me
everything you know of him.
It's a deal, but we go back a
long way, so there's a lot to tell
Just how long were you and
he together? Let's see,
I was his partner in battle for two years,
then we dated properly
for a year and a half.
And for two weeks, we even lived together.
Is that so?
Well, I fought by his side for one
night But for the past six months,
I have lived with him
and taken care of him
Really? That long?
Excuse me?
Um, he was my mentor and I
cleaned his room for two months.
And I also learned sword skills from him.
He also brought me honey pies
from the Prancing Beer Café.
I know I didn't spend as much
time with him as either of you,
but I'd like to swap stories with you.
All right, you're more than welcome
to join us if you want, Rolier.
Pardon me for intruding, but would you
have room for one more in your group?
Hello there, I saw you at the meeting.
I am an Imperial Knight of Norlingarth,
and my name is Sword Alne Surlute.
I was going to wait until
after the battle to see him,
but since Kirito and I
share a bit of history,
I was most eager to see how he was faring.
Understandable, Chief Guard, Sir Lute.
How do you know, Kirito?
You may call me Lina if it
pleases you, Lady Knight.
Kirito is a primary trainee at the
North Senator Swordcraft Academy,
where I too was studying.
For one year, he served as my page.
We trained together, and in so doing,
I taught him some of my sword skills.
Okay, it already sounds like
you'll have tons of neat stories.
Welcome to the club, Lina.
What is it?
Back where we come from.
He's called Dual Wielding, Kirito. Really?
Perhaps we should start with you
telling us how we got that name.
uh
Head Li
Kiri de mo hey?
Ki to Ko bo re o chi ta.
Tsuyo ga ri?
It's so sad that
I can't
live alone,
so I can't live alone,
so I can't
live alone.
Oh
I'm still here in any place.
I'm still here
Next time, the number of choices?